<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>22</id>
    <uid>125</uid>
    <im/>
    <ti>Terms of Use</ti>
    <ti1/>
    <url>terms-of-use</url>
    <link/>
    <opp>1</opp>
    <pa>1</pa>
    <ism>0</ism>
    <ct/>
    <so>0</so>
    <nv>0</nv>
    <st>2</st>
    <ti_vi>TERMS OF USE</ti_vi>
    <ti_en>TERMS OF USE</ti_en>
  </db>
  <more>
    <description>
      <vi>&lt;div class="single-page m-t-15"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="row"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="col-sm-3"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="block cmp-more no-m-top"&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/about-us"&gt;About us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/employer"&gt;Pricing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/privacy-policy"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="active" href="#"&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/contact"&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="col-sm-9"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="cmp-more no-m-top single-page-content"&gt;&#13;
&lt;h1 class="t-s-21 text-color1 text-bold no-margin"&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/h1&gt;&#13;
&lt;article class="m-t-15"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our Service allows you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information, text, graphics, videos, or other material ("Content"). You are responsible for the Content that you post to the Service, including its legality, reliability, and appropriateness.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;By posting Content to the Service, you grant us the right and license to use, modify, publicly perform, publicly display, reproduce, and distribute such Content on and through the Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You retain any and all of your rights to any Content you submit, post or display on or through the Service and you are responsible for protecting those rights. You agree that this license includes the right for us to make your Content available to other users of the Service, who may also use your Content subject to these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You represent and warrant that: (i) the Content is yours (you own it) or you have the right to use it and grant us the rights and license as provided in these Terms, and (ii) the posting of your Content on or through the Service does not violate the privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, contract rights or any other rights of any person.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;When you create an account with us, you must provide us information that is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes a breach of the Terms, which may result in immediate termination of your account on our Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Service and for any activities or actions under your password, whether your password is with our Service or a third-party service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You may not use as a username the name of another person or entity or that is not lawfully available for use, a name or trade mark that is subject to any rights of another person or entity other than you without appropriate authorization, or a name that is otherwise offensive, vulgar or obscene.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Service and its original content (excluding Content provided by users), features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of Thue.today and its licensors. The Service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the Viet Nam and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of Thue.today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our Service may contain links to third-party websites or services that are not owned or controlled by Thue.today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thue.today has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that Thue.today shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such websites or services.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party websites or services that you visit.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We may terminate or suspend your account immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach the Terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Upon termination, your right to use the Service will immediately cease. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service by deleting the account.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In using Thue.today, you must behave in a civil and respectful manner at all times. Further, you will not: Harass or stalk any other person; Harm or exploit minors; Act in a deceptive manner by, among other things, impersonating any person; Collect information about others; You will not express or imply that any statements you make are endorsed by Thue.today without our specific prior written consent. You will not distribute spam, and will not use any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other manual or automatic device or process to retrieve, index, "data mine", or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Service or its contents.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You will not post, distribute or reproduce in any way any copyrighted material, trademarks, or other proprietary information without obtaining the prior consent of the owner of such proprietary rights.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You will not interfere with or disrupt the services or the site or the servers or networks connected to the services or the site. You will not post, email or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment. Thue.today has the right, but not the obligation, to monitor all conduct on and content submitted to Thue.today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In no event shall Thue.today, nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the Service; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the Service; (iii) any content obtained from the Service; and (iv) unauthorized access, use or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thue.today its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER THUE.TODAY USERS. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT THUE.TODAY CURRENTLY DOES NOT CONDUCT CRIMINAL BACKGROUND CHECKS ON ITS USERS. THUE.TODAY ALSO DOES NOT INQUIRE INTO THE BACKGROUNDS OF ALL OF ITS USERS OR ATTEMPT TO VERIFY THE STATEMENTS OF ITS USERS. THUE.TODAY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE CONDUCT OF USERS OR THEIR COMPATIBILITY WITH ANY CURRENT OR FUTURE USER. THUE.TODAY PTE. LTD. RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CONDUCT ANY CRIMINAL BACKGROUND CHECK OR OTHER SCREENINGS (SUCH AS SEX OFFENDER REGISTER SEARCHES), AT ANY TIME AND USING AVAILABLE PUBLIC RECORDS.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;b. IN NO EVENT SHALL THUE.TODAY BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, WHETHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, GENERAL, SPECIAL, EMEPLARY, COMPENSATORY, CONSEQUENTIAL, AND/OR INCIDENTAL, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE CONDUCT OF YOU OR ANYONE ELSE IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE SERVICE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, BODILY INJURY, DEATH, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, AND/OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES RESULTING FROM COMMUNICATIONS OR MEETINGS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE THUE.TODAY SERVICE OR PERSONS YOU MEET THROUGH THUE.TODAY. YOU AGREE TO TAKE REASONABLE PRECAUTIONS IN ALL INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICE, PARTICULARLY IF YOU DECIDE TO MEET OFFLINE OR IN PERSON.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Viet Nam, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;All hires made as a result of Thue.today connection should abide the labor laws of the country/countries of both parties. We encourage both parties to get into a contractual agreement before commencing work or providing services.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 7 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;team@thue.today&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/article&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;</vi>
      <en>&lt;div class="single-page m-t-15"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="row"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="col-sm-3"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="block cmp-more no-m-top"&gt;&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/about-us"&gt;About us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/employer"&gt;Pricing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/privacy-policy"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="active" href="#"&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="/page/contact"&gt;Contact us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="col-sm-9"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div class="cmp-more no-m-top single-page-content"&gt;&#13;
&lt;h1 class="t-s-21 text-color1 text-bold no-margin"&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/h1&gt;&#13;
&lt;article class="m-t-15"&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our Service allows you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information, text, graphics, videos, or other material ("Content"). You are responsible for the Content that you post to the Service, including its legality, reliability, and appropriateness.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;By posting Content to the Service, you grant us the right and license to use, modify, publicly perform, publicly display, reproduce, and distribute such Content on and through the Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You retain any and all of your rights to any Content you submit, post or display on or through the Service and you are responsible for protecting those rights. You agree that this license includes the right for us to make your Content available to other users of the Service, who may also use your Content subject to these Terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You represent and warrant that: (i) the Content is yours (you own it) or you have the right to use it and grant us the rights and license as provided in these Terms, and (ii) the posting of your Content on or through the Service does not violate the privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, contract rights or any other rights of any person.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;When you create an account with us, you must provide us information that is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes a breach of the Terms, which may result in immediate termination of your account on our Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Service and for any activities or actions under your password, whether your password is with our Service or a third-party service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You may not use as a username the name of another person or entity or that is not lawfully available for use, a name or trade mark that is subject to any rights of another person or entity other than you without appropriate authorization, or a name that is otherwise offensive, vulgar or obscene.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;The Service and its original content (excluding Content provided by users), features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of Thue.today and its licensors. The Service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the Viet Nam and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of Thue.today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our Service may contain links to third-party websites or services that are not owned or controlled by Thue.today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thue.today has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that Thue.today shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such websites or services.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party websites or services that you visit.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We may terminate or suspend your account immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach the Terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Upon termination, your right to use the Service will immediately cease. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service by deleting the account.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In using Thue.today, you must behave in a civil and respectful manner at all times. Further, you will not: Harass or stalk any other person; Harm or exploit minors; Act in a deceptive manner by, among other things, impersonating any person; Collect information about others; You will not express or imply that any statements you make are endorsed by Thue.today without our specific prior written consent. You will not distribute spam, and will not use any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other manual or automatic device or process to retrieve, index, "data mine", or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Service or its contents.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You will not post, distribute or reproduce in any way any copyrighted material, trademarks, or other proprietary information without obtaining the prior consent of the owner of such proprietary rights.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;You will not interfere with or disrupt the services or the site or the servers or networks connected to the services or the site. You will not post, email or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment. Thue.today has the right, but not the obligation, to monitor all conduct on and content submitted to Thue.today.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;In no event shall Thue.today, nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the Service; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the Service; (iii) any content obtained from the Service; and (iv) unauthorized access, use or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Thue.today its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER THUE.TODAY USERS. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT THUE.TODAY CURRENTLY DOES NOT CONDUCT CRIMINAL BACKGROUND CHECKS ON ITS USERS. THUE.TODAY ALSO DOES NOT INQUIRE INTO THE BACKGROUNDS OF ALL OF ITS USERS OR ATTEMPT TO VERIFY THE STATEMENTS OF ITS USERS. THUE.TODAY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE CONDUCT OF USERS OR THEIR COMPATIBILITY WITH ANY CURRENT OR FUTURE USER. THUE.TODAY PTE. LTD. RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CONDUCT ANY CRIMINAL BACKGROUND CHECK OR OTHER SCREENINGS (SUCH AS SEX OFFENDER REGISTER SEARCHES), AT ANY TIME AND USING AVAILABLE PUBLIC RECORDS.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;b. IN NO EVENT SHALL THUE.TODAY BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, WHETHER DIRECT, INDIRECT, GENERAL, SPECIAL, EMEPLARY, COMPENSATORY, CONSEQUENTIAL, AND/OR INCIDENTAL, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE CONDUCT OF YOU OR ANYONE ELSE IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE SERVICE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, BODILY INJURY, DEATH, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, AND/OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES RESULTING FROM COMMUNICATIONS OR MEETINGS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE THUE.TODAY SERVICE OR PERSONS YOU MEET THROUGH THUE.TODAY. YOU AGREE TO TAKE REASONABLE PRECAUTIONS IN ALL INTERACTIONS WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SERVICE, PARTICULARLY IF YOU DECIDE TO MEET OFFLINE OR IN PERSON.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Viet Nam, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;All hires made as a result of Thue.today connection should abide the labor laws of the country/countries of both parties. We encourage both parties to get into a contractual agreement before commencing work or providing services.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 7 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Service.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;team@thue.today&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;/article&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;&#13;
&lt;/div&gt;</en>
    </description>
  </more>
  <meta>
    <title>
      <vi>Dieu khoan su dung</vi>
      <en>TERMS OF USE</en>
    </title>
    <desc>
      <vi/>
      <en/>
    </desc>
    <keyword>
      <vi/>
      <en/>
    </keyword>
  </meta>
</information>
