<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <totalJob>
    <total>4</total>
    <strji>1,55,57,58</strji>
  </totalJob>
  <more>
    <about>&lt;p&gt;Hơn 15 năm tạo dựng và phát tri&amp;ecirc;̉n chu&amp;ocirc;̃i nhà hàng phục vụ Gà rán Kentucky tại Việt Nam theo tiêu chu&amp;acirc;̉n qu&amp;ocirc;́c t&amp;ecirc;́ của tập đoàn Yum! International, KFC Việt Nam đang phát tri&amp;ecirc;̉n không ngừng, ti&amp;ecirc;́p tục chinh phục các thị trường ti&amp;ecirc;̀m năng trên khắp các tỉnh, thành của cả nước. K&amp;ecirc;́ hoạch phát tri&amp;ecirc;̉n đ&amp;ecirc;́n năm 2015, KFC Việt Nam sẽ đạt con s&amp;ocirc;́ 200 nhà hàng trong khắp cả nước. Bên cạnh đó,chúng tôi sẽ mang đ&amp;ecirc;́n hơn 7000 việc làm và cơ hội đào tạo cho người dân Việt Nam.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;Những thành công của KFC Việt nam có được hôm nay, được tạo dựng nhờ vào đội ngũ nhân viên trẻ trung, năng động đang s&amp;ocirc;́ng và làm việc h&amp;ecirc;́t mình với văn hoá &amp;ldquo;How We Win Together&amp;rdquo; nhằm hướng đ&amp;ecirc;́n mục tiêu xây dựng KFC Việt Nam trở thành một Công ty có môi trường làm việc tuyệt vời.&lt;/p&gt;</about>
    <whyworkus>&lt;p&gt;WORK LIFE BALANCE&lt;br /&gt;Having a job that allows you the flexibility to enjoy the things that life has to offer is a definite tick in the box. At KFC we work to live. We endeavour to make your working life just as worthwhile as life outside work. You can be yourself and enjoy a supportive culture that promotes camaraderie.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;DISCOUNTS&lt;br /&gt;As a KFC employee you&amp;rsquo;ll be entitled to a discount on products. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive a staff discount card detailing the discounts you can enjoy when you join the team.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;SERVICE RECOGNITION&lt;br /&gt;From the day you join us, we recognise every day you spend with us. The rewards vary from badges to acknowledge your years of service to framed certificates and special gifts to show we appreciate the significant milestones you&amp;rsquo;ve reached.&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&lt;p&gt;EDUCATION ASSISTANCE&lt;br /&gt;For those employees wanting to embark on tertiary education, KFC may contribute towards your education and textbook fees. Full-time employees and in some cases, part-time members of the Restaurant Management team, are currently eligible for this assistance.&lt;/p&gt;</whyworkus>
  </more>
  <saveuser>
    <total>9</total>
    <strui>39,3,31,50,49,48,52,58,36</strui>
  </saveuser>
  <companybanner>1_kfc-cover.png</companybanner>
  <db>
    <id>1</id>
    <ui>1</ui>
    <name>KFC Vietnam</name>
    <url>kfcvietnam</url>
    <im>1_kfc-avatar.jpg</im>
    <category>14,15,16</category>
    <phone>0944112199</phone>
    <address>97/1 Le Quang Dinh</address>
    <city>30</city>
    <website>http://facebook.com</website>
    <skype/>
    <facebook>https://www.facebook.com/KFCVietnam</facebook>
    <size>1</size>
    <status>2</status>
    <dayleft>1472301876</dayleft>
    <jobleft>16</jobleft>
    <fb_load_newfeed>0</fb_load_newfeed>
    <fb_load_photo>0</fb_load_photo>
    <created>1453001649</created>
    <deactive>0</deactive>
    <district/>
    <district_text_vi/>
    <district_text_en/>
  </db>
  <latlng>
    <lat>10.763737058394662</lat>
    <lng>106.77607230840749</lng>
  </latlng>
</information>
