<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>221</id>
    <ui>297</ui>
    <name>XU Restaurant Lounge</name>
    <url>XuSaigon</url>
    <im>180328248754299_xu-restaurant-lounge.jpg</im>
    <im_banner>180328248754299_xu-restaurant-lounge-cover.jpg</im_banner>
    <category>14,16</category>
    <phone/>
    <address>75 Hai Ba Trung street, district 1, hcm city</address>
    <district>0</district>
    <district_text_vi/>
    <district_text_en/>
    <city>30</city>
    <lat>10.7770629</lat>
    <lng>106.7044555</lng>
    <website>xusaigon.com</website>
    <about/>
    <facebook>https://www.facebook.com/XuSaigon/</facebook>
    <size>1</size>
    <status>0</status>
    <fb_load_newfeed>1</fb_load_newfeed>
    <fb_load_photo>1</fb_load_photo>
    <created>1468404430</created>
  </db>
  <more>
    <about> Xu Restaurant on level one, this seated dining area serves Modern Family Style (shared plate) menu that offers Modern Vietnamese dishes that are designed for sharing among friends &amp; family and are brought to the table steadily and continuously throughout the meal that used quality local produce from south to north of Vietnam.  \r\n\r\nThe lounge on the ground floor offers unique Vietnamese inspired cocktails &amp; beverages, Vietnamese small bites menu &amp; an extensive wine list. \r\n\r\nWhether it’s an intimate dinner for two, dinner with friends, a corporate event or a group party booking, a special event from standup cocktail and canapeù event to sit down dinners, Xu Restaurant Lounge brings together all of the essential elements for a perfect Vietnamese dining experience and is ideal for creating a unique experience for your next event. \r\n\r\nFor outside event, let Xu devise a unique menu of food and drinks, prepare and organize a stunning presentation, and provide trained and attentive staff so you can relax and spend time with your guests.\r\n\r\nFor information about our Set Menus, Canapeù Menu &amp; Beverage Packages please contact Xu at info@xusaigon.com or +848 3824 8468 .\r\n\r\nXu Restaurant Lounge is open every day of the year from 11:30am until Midnight. Lunch is served from 11:30am until 2:30pm and Dinner is from 6:00pm until 11:00pm. \r\n\r\n \'EATING IS SUSTENANCE FOR THE BODY, DINING IS THE ART OF LIVING’\r\n </about>
    <whyworkus/>
  </more>
  <companybanner>180328248754299_xu-restaurant-lounge-cover.jpg</companybanner>
  <totalJob>
    <total>3</total>
    <strji>101,238,362</strji>
  </totalJob>
  <pagecmpfacebookcover>221_xu-banner.jpg</pagecmpfacebookcover>
</information>
