<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>362</id>
    <ui>4132</ui>
    <name>SONG NGƯ Seafood Restaurant</name>
    <url>songngu70</url>
    <im>_song-ngu-seafood-restaurant.jpg</im>
    <im_banner>_song-ngu-seafood-restaurant-cover.jpg</im_banner>
    <category>14</category>
    <phone>+84-8-38325017</phone>
    <address>70 - 72 Sương Nguyệt Ánh Street, Bến Thành Ward, District 1</address>
    <district>0</district>
    <district_text_vi/>
    <district_text_en/>
    <city>30</city>
    <lat>10.772588</lat>
    <lng>106.689430</lng>
    <website>http://www.songngu.com</website>
    <about/>
    <facebook>https://www.facebook.com/songngu70/</facebook>
    <facebook_cover/>
    <size>1</size>
    <status>0</status>
    <fb_load_newfeed>1</fb_load_newfeed>
    <fb_load_photo>1</fb_load_photo>
    <created>1474981514</created>
  </db>
  <more>
    <about>Locating right in middle of Saigon downtown, at 70 Suong Nguyet Anh, District 1, Song Ngu Restaurant, a twinned villa with a vast garden on an area more than 1,000 m 2, divided into 8 different dining rooms, welcomes from 350 to 400 guests every night.&#13;
&#13;
Song Ngu Restaurant has been established since 1996 and become famous for its delicious, Vietnamese authentic and diversified menu. It offers wide range of dishes, cooked from fresh seafood such as shrimps, crabs, fish…; all have passed the severe tests for hygiene, freshness and quality.&#13;
&#13;
Many menu items have been well known beyond the border to neighbor countries Japan, Korea, China, Malaysia and Taiwan…; such as lobster congee, mantis shrimp fried with garlic and crab spring roll&#13;
&#13;
Besides food, Song Ngu Restaurant introduces many aspects of the Vietnamese culture and gastronomy to all nationals, expatriates and foreigners, presenting to them the diverse aspects of Vietnamese culture, gastronomy, decoration art, and also the particular character of Vietnamese people. Everyday traditional Vietnamese music is performed by an orchestra with ladies wearing the traditional “Ao Dai” and playing with traditional instruments.&#13;
&#13;
Song Ngu Restaurant is the ideal venue for meeting with friends in an intimate and healthy ambiance. Not only businessmen and high income family, but also the high graded leaders of Vietnam have always chosen us for hosting their. We have been honored welcomed Prime Minister of Japan, President of Bulgaria, President of Ireland and Vice Prime Minister from Denmark. Furthermore, there are 5 foreigner television stations have filmed Song Ngu to promote Vietnamese authentic cuisine to their audience.</about>
    <whyworkus/>
  </more>
  <companybanner>_song-ngu-seafood-restaurant-cover.jpg</companybanner>
  <totalJob>
    <total>2</total>
    <strji>353,354</strji>
  </totalJob>
</information>
