<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>135</id>
    <ui>567</ui>
    <ci>247</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Waiter/ Waitress</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>2</le>
    <ty>1,4</ty>
    <ex>1</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>0</sn>
    <s1>3000000</s1>
    <s2>5000000</s2>
    <s3>136</s3>
    <s4>227</s4>
    <lo/>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>67</location_id>
    <lat>0.000000</lat>
    <lng>0.000000</lng>
    <de>2016-10-06</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1470554576</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>1.	Professional customer service skills:&#13;
•	Greeting Guests,  presenting menus,  making food recommendations and answering questions regarding food and beverages&#13;
•	Taking orders and relaying to kitchen and bar staff&#13;
•	Using point of sale system&#13;
•	Processing cash and credit card payments&#13;
2.	Able to quickly learn new menu items and new service procedures&#13;
3.	Familiar with different kinds of food and beverages &#13;
4.	Clear communication skills - verbal and written&#13;
5.	Ability to speak and write in English an advantage&#13;
6.	Accurate with attention to detail&#13;
7.	Team-player&#13;
8.	Honest and respectful at all times&#13;
9.	High standard of personal presentation,  cleanliness and personal hygiene&#13;
10.	Physically able to stand for long periods and lift heavy trays</requirement>
    <description>As a member of our team of Ladies and Gentlemen serving Ladies and Gentlemen you will serve Guests by taking orders, serving food and preparing tables. &#13;
The most important part of your work is to make Guests feel welcome and comfortable when they arrive, during their meal, and when they leave. &#13;
Even though you may join us with experience from somewhere else you will participate in our intensive career path road map training program to ready you for promotion in 1 year. &#13;
</description>
    <benefit>•	Our staff work an 8-hour roster, which may include split shifts.&#13;
•	In addition to salary and split shift payments our staff may receive tips and bonuses&#13;
•	12 days paid holidays per year after 12 months&#13;
•	Staff meal, bike parking and other benefits&#13;
•	Great training program to help you develop the professional skills for a long term career in hospitality</benefit>
    <keyword>waiter/waitress</keyword>
  </more>
</information>
