<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>196</id>
    <ui>1366</ui>
    <ci>283</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>F&amp;B Manager</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>5</le>
    <ty>1</ty>
    <ex>2</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>0</sn>
    <s1>9000000</s1>
    <s2>11000000</s2>
    <s3>409</s3>
    <s4>500</s4>
    <lo/>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14,15</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>vi,en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>106</location_id>
    <lat>0.000000</lat>
    <lng>0.000000</lng>
    <de>2016-10-25</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1472191762</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>familiar with leadership, food and beverage, customer service.&#13;
Good written and spoken English and Vietnamese.&#13;
Able to work weekend.</requirement>
    <description>The F&amp;B manager is responsible for the daily operations of the cafe. He’ll ensure that the staff is working together as a team to ensure optimum service and quality and that guest needs are met. &#13;
&#13;
Staff&#13;
Lead a team who’s better than you at what they do.&#13;
&#13;
1. Hiring, training, and motivating awesome staff.&#13;
2. Recommend people for hiring, promotion, and, if need be, firing.&#13;
3. Maintaining high standards of quality control, hygiene, health and safety.&#13;
4. Conduct daily briefings.&#13;
&#13;
Organization&#13;
Keep things running smoothly.&#13;
&#13;
1. Plan staff, menu, ingredients, communication, set-up for events&#13;
2. Open/close the shop like it’s the first day. Make sure everything’s perfect. No “doodads”.&#13;
&#13;
Catering &#13;
1. Work with the kitchen to plan for the events. Come up with a catering menu. &#13;
2. Make sure that the staff knows what to do during the event. Check that everything is running smoothly. &#13;
3. Settle the bill at the end of the event with the organizer.  &#13;
&#13;
Host&#13;
Be present and meticulous.&#13;
&#13;
1. Walk around. Talk to people. Remove “doodads”. Rearrange chairs. Take a step back and look at the operation, is everything/everyone where it’s supposed to be? Greet and welcome customers, give them a tour. Recommending menu items. &#13;
2. Managing customer’s complaints or feedback. &#13;
3. Maintain the image of WORK Saigon. Professional, but relaxed. &#13;
4. Think of cool menu items/promotions to offer.</description>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword>Customer service,Problem-solving,Responsibility,Team-work</keyword>
  </more>
  <userapplied>
    <total>13</total>
    <strui>1440,1354,2449,680,853,3133,3275,3509,3977,4313,5228,5911,7018</strui>
  </userapplied>
</information>
