<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>211</id>
    <ui>1554</ui>
    <ci>295</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Waiter/ Waitress</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>2</le>
    <ty>1,2</ty>
    <ex>1</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>0</sn>
    <s1>4000000</s1>
    <s2>5000000</s2>
    <s3>181</s3>
    <s4>227</s4>
    <lo/>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14,16</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>118</location_id>
    <lat>0.000000</lat>
    <lng>0.000000</lng>
    <de>2016-10-29</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1472529651</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>•	Education: High school diploma &#13;
•	Experience in hotel and/or restaurant services essential&#13;
•	Must be service-minded to meet customer needs&#13;
•	Must possess some F&amp;B product knowledge&#13;
•	Good communication both in English &amp; Vietnamese&#13;
•	Having experience at the same position is preferred&#13;
</requirement>
    <description>•	To deliver Food and Beverage service of high standard and in accordance with standards and procedures.&#13;
•	To provide efficient, expedient and courteous to guest leading to total the guest and company satisfaction.&#13;
•	To prepare for service by ensuring the department’s:&#13;
o	Grooming is impeccable and in accordance with the company standards &#13;
Ensure that outlet is ready for service and guest comfort (music is on, lighting is on, glassware is polished, the restaurant is clean, etc.)&#13;
o	Check up all the items needed before putting it in use. Be responsibly minded for the breakage and loss of such items. &#13;
o	To lay up the table, side station, bar counter, mezzanine. To ensure all the items required for the set-up are clean, unspotted and in place. &#13;
•	To be courteous, warm and smiling while dealing with guest. Be efficient and fast and serve with confidence and flair.&#13;
•	Must be familiar with all menu items, their preparation and service procedure.&#13;
•	To listen guest’s complaints. Rectify wrong doings and report to Supervisor/ Assistant Restaurant Manager all the comments from Guests.&#13;
•	Be able to regularly pass training examinations&#13;
•	Assist team members with sections and work if all work in their assigned section is taken care of&#13;
•	To handle other task when assigned by the company.&#13;
</description>
    <benefit>_ 13th salaray &#13;
_ Working in a professional and dyamic enviroment &#13;
_ 12 days annual leave per year &#13;
_ Annual Company Party, Company Trip </benefit>
    <keyword/>
  </more>
  <userapplied>
    <total>88</total>
    <strui>1134,1763,355,1803,1817,1828,1881,390,941,1992,1991,1751,1773,1480,2065,350,1958,2157,1546,2199,2219,2257,2260,2432,1742,2471,2106,2532,2546,2159,2746,2715,2995,3026,3075,3148,3177,3174,3213,3215,3133,3221,3239,3315,3353,3422,425,292,1706,3690,3955,4205,4255,4266,4042,4360,4377,4408,2786,4343,4625,4724,4813,4708,4867,4150,5005,3207,5193,5226,4474,5728,5770,5911,5945,6193,6243,6279,6295,6319,6433,4402,6966,5107,7593,5255,3293,7795</strui>
  </userapplied>
</information>
