<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>217</id>
    <ui>1558</ui>
    <ci>297</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Human Resources Officer</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>2</le>
    <ty>1</ty>
    <ex>2</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>1</sn>
    <s1>0</s1>
    <s2>0</s2>
    <s3>0</s3>
    <s4>0</s4>
    <lo/>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14,18,30</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>vi,en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>120</location_id>
    <lat>0.000000</lat>
    <lng>0.000000</lng>
    <de>2016-10-29</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1472542827</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>QUALIFICATIONS:&#13;
&#13;
	Human Resource background.&#13;
	Certification/License: No &#13;
	Minimum of one year experience handling in similar job environment. Preferably in the hospitality industry. &#13;
	Ability to work in a computer based, multi-task environment. &#13;
	Have ability to communicate fluently in the English language, both verbally and in writing.&#13;
&#13;
OTHER:&#13;
&#13;
Team spirit is much highlighted. Must have a perfect hygiene and grooming. Have ability to communicate in a polite way. Be able to communicate effectively at all levels. Must be ready and responsible when assigned to other related duties and or special projects as designated by Human Resources Manager or the Resort Management.&#13;
</requirement>
    <description>POSITION OVERVIEW:&#13;
&#13;
	To assist and responsible for administrative and general assignments from the Human Resource Manger and of the department. &#13;
	To ensure efficiency of the administration of the department. &#13;
&#13;
KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&#13;
&#13;
	Ensure that the day-to-day administrative needs of the department are fulfilled.&#13;
	Perform the duties within the framework defined by the norms of the Company and within the Resort’s internal regulations.&#13;
	Keep confidential information CONFIDENTIAL.&#13;
	Responsible for rendering secretarial and clerical services for the Human Resource Manager as required. &#13;
	Organize and maintain HR filling system, update staff profile.&#13;
	Record personal income tax , family tax reduction &#13;
	Making report to local police monthly&#13;
	Periodically report to Department of Labor, Invalid and Social Affairs for employee social &amp; health insurance.&#13;
	Keeps record of all hotel items issued to the staff such as uniform, nametag, and etc….&#13;
	Keeps record all leave application of staff such as annual, sick, public holiday, overtime...&#13;
	Keep all records related to staff, job training and other records&#13;
	To prepare correspondence such as fax, letter, memo, complimentary voucher, etc as assigned with a coding system for tracking.&#13;
	To maintain office supplies stock.&#13;
	Input data into computer system as required.&#13;
	To handle incoming/ outgoing telephone calls and faxes.&#13;
	To handle all contact listings such as Owner contacts, Resort contacts and other supplier companies, etc. &#13;
	Be understanding and supportive, encouraging and helpful to all.&#13;
	Have a good working relationship with all colleagues.&#13;
	To perform special duties as required by the Human Resource Manager.&#13;
&#13;
The above key areas &amp; responsibilities reflect the items considered necessary to describe the principal functions of the job identified and shall not be construed as a detailed description of all the work requirements that may be inherent in the job.&#13;
</description>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
  </more>
  <userapplied>
    <total>1</total>
    <strui>3322</strui>
  </userapplied>
</information>
