<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>218</id>
    <ui>1558</ui>
    <ci>297</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Chief Maintenance</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>5</le>
    <ty>1</ty>
    <ex>5</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>1</sn>
    <s1>0</s1>
    <s2>0</s2>
    <s3>0</s3>
    <s4>0</s4>
    <lo/>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14,18,30</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>vi,en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>120</location_id>
    <lat>0.000000</lat>
    <lng>0.000000</lng>
    <de>2016-10-29</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1472542988</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>QUALIFICATIONS:&#13;
&#13;
	Technical Degree&#13;
	Certification/ license: yes&#13;
	At least 5 years experience handling and managing the Maintenance operation with the same position in international resort. &#13;
	Ability to work in a computer based, multi-task environment. &#13;
	Languages: fluent in English both verbal and writing.&#13;
&#13;
OTHER:&#13;
&#13;
Be able to communicate effectively at all levels. Be alert and responsible, the business functions seven days a week, 24 hours a day. A hospitable service atmosphere must be projected at all the time. As the business demands the Food &amp; Beverage Director must render his/her dedication to the job. To perform other related duties and special projects as required by General Manager.&#13;
</requirement>
    <description>POSITION OVERVIEW:&#13;
&#13;
	To take overall charge for the repair and preventive maintenance of mechanical and electrical services, general building maintenance and absolute priority fire prevention system. &#13;
	Teach all Engineering staff theoretically and practically. &#13;
&#13;
KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&#13;
&#13;
	To ensure that all repairs and preventive maintenance schedules are carried out according to schedule. &#13;
	Responsible for safety of the resort and staff.&#13;
	Preventive Maintenance for Chiller circuits and Chiller water, Steam System, Air handling units, Fire fighting facilities and equipments and concerned equipment as Laundry machines and other equipment which needs regular maintenance.&#13;
	Monthly reports according to company policy, all utilities consumption, staff weekly roster, medical or vacation leave, correspondence, purchase requests, store control and inventory, analyzing of complaints, log books and various checklists, handling of repair &amp; job orders, hold regular meetings or briefings with staff.&#13;
	Follow up the operation of all equipments and have action immediately for repairing or replacement if needed.&#13;
	Check after the staff assignments work for good result.&#13;
	Create preventive maintenance schedule due to the resort occupancy condition and the working time of equipments.&#13;
	Assist, inspect and control in case of resort renovation.&#13;
	Ensure and coordinate with all departments for the energy saving program.&#13;
	Study the new global technology from supplier, other resorts…about equipment, device and the way of management to upgrade in the resort.&#13;
	Ensure, remind properly staff attitude toward guests while working.&#13;
	Control and maintain energy consumption in good saving and efficient.&#13;
	Ensure that all equipment &amp; machineries and resort facilities are well maintained.&#13;
	Select to replace the good and right equipments, devices and materials in low cost.&#13;
	Follow up, plan and adjust equipment operation for low energy consumption.&#13;
	Have the schedule of staff training for each section yearly to improve professional career.&#13;
	Evaluate, promote and remind the staffs on time when she/he does the good job or makes mistake.&#13;
	Is responsible for staff grooming and attire.&#13;
	Conduct the meeting, briefing for all staffs at regular intervals for information purposes.&#13;
	Ensure a good atmosphere and good efficiency co-operation in his department.&#13;
	To ensure responsibilities for InterREACT are fully understood&#13;
	To take responsibilities for report directly to the General Manager for InterREACT mamangement.&#13;
	To take responsibilities for the safe operation of employees, contractors and volunteers, guests&#13;
	Ensure that the OHS&amp;E policies and procedures are effectively communicated to all employees, contractors and volunteers and the control of visitors to worksites.&#13;
	Ensure induction and department or job specific training is provided for all employees, contractors and volunteers.&#13;
	Ensure that Department Safety Procedures and other safety information are prepared and complied with.&#13;
	Ensure that Department safety plans are developed in consultation with employees.&#13;
	To take responsibilities for report directly to the General Manager for InterREACT mamangement in any Engineering and Maintenance related matters.&#13;
	To be responsible for setting policy, agreeing and providing resources and procedures for the OH&amp;S, EEO, Rehabilitation and Environmental programmes and monitoring performance to ensure that they are consistent with the policies and objectives.&#13;
	Set objectives and monitor key performance indicators regarding OH&amp;S, EEO, Rehabilitation and Environmental performance.&#13;
-	Agree an annual OH&amp;S, EEO, Rehabilitation and Environmental improvement plan.&#13;
-	Actively promote OH&amp;S, EEO, Rehabilitation and Environmental management. &#13;
-	Ensure that safety issues are resolved in consultation with employees.&#13;
-	Promote OH&amp;S, EEO, Rehabilitation and Environmental management by example.&#13;
-	To take responsibilities of Occupational Health &amp; Safety Committee members are defined by legislation and in particular their role is to monitor the Occupational Health &amp; Safety Management System and provide an avenue for consultation and resolution of safety issues. &#13;
-	Specific responsibilities for Occupational Health, Safety &amp; Rehabilitation are also contained in any specific procedures agreed at a location level.&#13;
-	Organisational accountabilities reflect these responsibilities.&#13;
	Be understanding and supportive, encouraging and helpful to all.&#13;
	Have a good working relationship with all colleagues.&#13;
&#13;
The above key areas &amp; responsibilities reflect the items considered necessary to describe the principal functions of the job identified and shall not be construed as a detailed description of all the work requirements that may be inherent in the job.&#13;
</description>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
  </more>
</information>
