<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>304</id>
    <ui>2643</ui>
    <ci>331</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Room Attendant/ CL - Nhân Viên Vệ Sinh Phòng/ Thời Vụ</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>2</le>
    <ty>4</ty>
    <ex>1</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>1</sn>
    <s1>0</s1>
    <s2>0</s2>
    <s3>0</s3>
    <s4>0</s4>
    <lo>30</lo>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14,20</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>171</location_id>
    <lat>10.776995</lat>
    <lng>10.776995</lng>
    <de>2016-11-12</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1474433674</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>High School degree.&#13;
English communication.&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
&#13;
</requirement>
    <description>Be responsible for keeping guestrooms and the surrounding area in clean, orderly and well-maintained condition.&#13;
 &#13;
DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES&#13;
1.	To report defects, unusual guest behaviour, sickness and any damage found in guestroom.&#13;
2.	To report and hand over lost and found articles to Floor Supervisor or Housekeeping office.&#13;
3.	To count soiled linen and store clean linen in floor pantry.&#13;
4.	To maintain cleanliness in floor pantry and back areas.&#13;
5.	To maintain cleanliness of trolleys and ensure that adequate supplies are maintained.&#13;
6.	To report suspicious persons loitering on guest corridors. &#13;
7.	To move furniture from one room to another, from rooms to maintenance rooms and vice versa.&#13;
9.	To render personal assistance to guest such as taking out food trays, shoe polishing, etc.&#13;
10.	To check mini-bar and refill daily consumption following the proper procedures.&#13;
11.	To inform fused light bulbs in guestrooms.&#13;
12.	To remove all room service trolleys or trays from corridors and guest rooms automatically.&#13;
13.	To attend to guest requests immediately.&#13;
14.	To deliver and collect guest laundry.&#13;
15.	To perform other duties as assigned by the superior.&#13;
16.	To maintain the cleanliness and tidiness of guest corridors, lift landing, lift doors and ashurns are up to standard.&#13;
17.	To tidy up the vacant rooms and make sure it is ready for guest arrival.&#13;
&#13;
Day Shift&#13;
1.	To make up dirty rooms and general cleaning.  &#13;
2.	To clean both the bedroom and bathroom.&#13;
3.	To change used bed linen daily.&#13;
4.	To vacuum room carpet daily.&#13;
5.	To change used bathroom towels daily.&#13;
6.	To report mini-bar consumption daily to the HK Clerk for record.&#13;
7.	To refill guestroom supplies and mini-bar daily.&#13;
8.	To pay special attention to VIP rooms.&#13;
9.	To clean and stock maid trolley at the end of the shift.&#13;
10.	To maintain and clean all equipment at the end of the shift. &#13;
11.	To check and report to superior if any discrepancy found regarding room status.   &#13;
12.	To perform other duties as assigned by the superior.&#13;
13.	To hand-over with the next shift and use maid logbook for daily communication as needed.</description>
    <benefit>Free laundry for staff uniforms, free duty meals, medical benefits and other benefits as and when may be provided by the Hotel.&#13;
</benefit>
    <keyword>Tinh thần trách nhiệm,Chịu được áp lực công việc,Nhiệt tình</keyword>
  </more>
  <userapplied>
    <total>12</total>
    <strui>3657,3744,4042,4879,5310,3509,3581,6025,6033,6495,6777,8012</strui>
  </userapplied>
</information>
