<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>341</id>
    <ui>3949</ui>
    <ci>358</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Bartender</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>2</le>
    <ty>1,4,6</ty>
    <ex>1</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>1</sn>
    <s1>5000000</s1>
    <s2>8000000</s2>
    <s3>227</s3>
    <s4>363</s4>
    <lo>30</lo>
    <co>vn,for</co>
    <ca>14,16</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>vi,en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>229</location_id>
    <lat>10.773604</lat>
    <lng>10.773604</lng>
    <de>2016-10-26</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1474901337</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>•	Demonstrated ability to interact with customers, employees and third parties that reflects highly on the hotel, the brand and the Company.  &#13;
•	Alcohol awareness certification and/or food service permit or valid health/food handler card as required by local government agency.  &#13;
•	Able to read and write English Qualifications  &#13;
•	High School or Vocational Certificate in Hotel Management, Food &amp; Beverage, or related field. . Experience  &#13;
•	1 years related experience or an equivalent combination of education and experience. Knowledge of liquor brands, beer, wine, champagne, non-alcoholic beverages, designated glassware, preparation methods and garnishments preferred</requirement>
    <description>•	Receives instructions from the Bar Supervisor on the various jobs to be carried out.  &#13;
•	Ensures smooth daily operation and cleanliness of his work area.  &#13;
•	Prepares bar requisitions and internal transfers for approval by the Head Department  &#13;
•	Assists the accounting staff during stocktaking i.e. setting up the bar to facilitate the inventory count.  &#13;
•	Prepare and serve drinks.  &#13;
•	Replenish juices and mixes.  &#13;
•	Cut limes, oranges and pineapple for garnishes.  &#13;
•	Clean all bottles and refrigerators daily.  &#13;
•	Flush out draft beer lines.  &#13;
•	Wipe down bar counter.  &#13;
•	Clean out ashtrays.</description>
    <benefit>• Professional working environment &#13;
• Attractive benefits that will be discuss directly during the interview</benefit>
    <keyword>Giao tiếp hiệu quả,Tập trung trong công việc,Chịu được áp lực công việc,Kỹ năng chăm sóc khách hàng,Kỹ năng giải quyết tình huống,Trung thực,Tự tin,Nhiệt tình,Tinh thần trách nhiệm,Tinh thần làm việc nhóm</keyword>
  </more>
  <userapplied>
    <total>13</total>
    <strui>4236,4255,3866,2224,4724,4623,4944,3207,5033,5398,6012,6272,7792</strui>
  </userapplied>
</information>
