<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>35</id>
    <ui>67</ui>
    <ci>67</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Bartender</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>1</le>
    <ty>1</ty>
    <ex>2</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>0</sn>
    <s1>8000000</s1>
    <s2>10000000</s2>
    <s3>363</s3>
    <s4>454</s4>
    <lo>30</lo>
    <ca>14</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <de>0000-00-00</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1460973743</cr>
    <la></la>
  </db>
  <more>
    <number>0908059590</number>
    <requirement>Cheerful and friendly looking / Ngọai hình ưa nhìn và thân thiện.&#13;
2. 1 year experience in similar position in restaurant or hotel, bar is an advantage / Kinh nghiệm 1&#13;
năm làm việc ở vị trí tương đương tại nhà hàng hoặc khách sạn, bar.&#13;
3. Able to communicate in English / Giao tiếp tiếng Anh cơ bản.&#13;
4. Positive attitude and team working spirit / Có thái độ tích cực và tinh thần tập thể.&#13;
5. Able to work night shift until 1am / Có thể làm đến 1 giờ khuya.</requirement>
    <description>1. Set and maintain par levels on all beverages.&#13;
2. Daily stock orders/requisitions.&#13;
3. Maintain equipment par level. Purchase equipment when required, with management authorization.&#13;
4. Fill out all stock transfers.&#13;
5. Fill out all spillage reports.&#13;
6. Responsible for daily cleaning of the bar.&#13;
7. Control all glassware, maintaining breakage reports, and liaise with the Stewarding Dept. to order more stock.&#13;
8. Ensure a thorough knowledge of the workings of your Department.&#13;
9. To understand and act on the duties pertaining to the opening of the bar.&#13;
10. To understand the correct method of taking an order and dispensing in the correct manner.&#13;
11. To implement correct portion control of beverage.&#13;
12. To have a practical working knowledge of all equipment within the bar.&#13;
13. To understand fundamental mixed drinks, cocktails and wines.&#13;
14. Conduct the correct procedures to secure the bar.&#13;
15. Monitor and understand production controls.&#13;
16. To follow the correct method of handling returned drinks.&#13;
17. Perform other duties as assigned by Supervisor / Manager.</description>
  </more>
</information>
