<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>381</id>
    <ui>229</ui>
    <ci>375</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Head of Design</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>5</le>
    <ty>1</ty>
    <ex>5</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>1</sn>
    <s1>0</s1>
    <s2>0</s2>
    <s3>0</s3>
    <s4>0</s4>
    <lo>30</lo>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14,15,16</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>vi,en</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>264</location_id>
    <lat>10.789796</lat>
    <lng>10.789796</lng>
    <de>2016-10-28</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1475490939</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>	Technical Skills: Must be fluent in Photoshop, Ai, Indesign&#13;
	Language Skills: Must be fluent in English and Vietnamese&#13;
	Confidence: Able to manage and lead other creative staff&#13;
	Technical Craftsmanship: Design wiz&#13;
	Enthusiast: Passionate about designing and delivering superb presentations using design, color concepts, typography, hierarchy and flow&#13;
	Professionalism: True professional in this field with the ability to relate well with all levels of AFG&#13;
</requirement>
    <description>Head of Design - Al Fresco’s Group Vietnam&#13;
Ready to make your next career move and head up the national design department of a dynamic market leader in Vietnam’s hospitality sector?&#13;
The Al Fresco’s Group Vietnam has grown over its 20 years in Vietnam to become a leading restaurant chain, currently with over 50 restaurants and 6 prime brands operating in Hanoi, Ho Chi Minh City and Danang. &#13;
If you think you can provide cool, calm and inspiring leadership to our national design team when the pressure is really on; when the deadlines are insane, and when the workload just keeps growing, then we want to hear from you.&#13;
The position is based in HCMC and reports to the Group Marketing Manager also based in HCMC. Your design team of 3 staff are in Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi and so some travel to Hanoi /Danang will be a requirement. And you will normally work 5.5 days per week.  &#13;
Salary will be negotiable and based on the talent you can bring to our Group. &#13;
Summary of key responsibilities and accountabilities:&#13;
1.	Managing and developing the AFG Design Department in SGN/HN and DAN., including managing and tasking the 3 design team staff in HCMC &amp; HN&#13;
2.	Developing and implement a new production system for the design department to ensure clear and easy understanding of your dept.’s work scheduling&#13;
3.	Liaising with brand managers, restaurant managers and endeavoring to provide them with the best possible support from the AFG design team.&#13;
4.	Contributing to and developing marketing plans and strategies of the AFG with the Group Marketing Manager and Marketing Team&#13;
5.	Working with the Group Marketing Manager to support the Southern &amp; Northern Area Managers and other senior managers in AFG.&#13;
6.	Developing design briefs by gathering information and data to clarify design issues.&#13;
7.	Applying creativity to produce new ideas using a wide range of media, including photography, movies and computer aided design&#13;
8.	Setting the standard for the design team in producing accurate and high quality work within tight deadlines.&#13;
9.	Contributing ideas and design artwork to the overall brief Liaising with printers and other suppliers&#13;
10.	Mentoring your colleagues and maintaining a sense of humor when everyone around you is losing theirs. &#13;
</description>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
  </more>
  <userapplied>
    <total>1</total>
    <strui>853</strui>
  </userapplied>
</information>
