<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <db>
    <id>519</id>
    <ui>1671</ui>
    <ci>398</ci>
    <ai>0</ai>
    <ti>Cashier</ti>
    <ta/>
    <le>2</le>
    <ty>1</ty>
    <ex>1</ex>
    <sa>1</sa>
    <sn>0</sn>
    <s1>4000000</s1>
    <s2>4500000</s2>
    <s3>181</s3>
    <s4>204</s4>
    <lo>30</lo>
    <co>vn</co>
    <ca>14,15</ca>
    <vi>0</vi>
    <so>0</so>
    <st>2</st>
    <pi>0</pi>
    <la>vi</la>
    <description/>
    <requirement/>
    <workhour/>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
    <ad/>
    <location_id>315</location_id>
    <lat>10.775751</lat>
    <lng>10.775751</lng>
    <de>2016-12-15</de>
    <re>0000-00-00</re>
    <cr>1477384298</cr>
  </db>
  <more>
    <requirement>    Cashier is required to in charge direct on cash, invoice and any related matter. Ensure to follow up with company’s cash handling procedures. Maintain confidentiality of proprietary information, protect company assets and focus on security, exactly process on any financial cases.&#13;
    Receiving and hand over all cash, invoice, card, cash float and ensure that will be work in good operation.&#13;
    Get accurate information from staff to proceed in bill payments for customers when requested. Ensure adequate recognition and counting invoiced correctly then process guests return excess cash, if any.&#13;
    Regular updates list membership card, guests discounts or payment cards policy to implement the discount price for each level according to specific regulations. Always check the expiry date and signature for comparison in case of necessity.&#13;
    Issue red invoice (VAT) as customers requirement. Check the carefully of billing information, tracking and billing for guests. Save the relevant documents such as serial number, date .. in the logbook for comparison when necessary. Always perform this task carefully and follow the policies.&#13;
    Check and compare actual cash, card and sales report, ensure that follow instruction.&#13;
    Ensure that Safety and security  procedures are follow in cases. Depend on transfer to Bank account or submit by cash.&#13;
    Daily report will be printed out as requirement.</requirement>
    <description>Graduate from any related major&#13;
01 year experience with same position&#13;
Adapability/ Flexibility/ Positive manner and honestly.&#13;
Good in English communication&#13;
Good in computer skill and POS system.</description>
    <workhour>The Cashier will normally work 48 hours each week. </workhour>
    <benefit/>
    <keyword/>
  </more>
  <userapplied>
    <total>4</total>
    <strui>7425,5107,7872,2897</strui>
  </userapplied>
</information>
