<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <userinfo>
    <db>
      <id>3293</id>
      <email>kimthiennong@gmail.com</email>
      <username/>
      <name>Nông Thiên Kim</name>
      <im>3293_fotor-14418904121280.jpg</im>
      <gender>2</gender>
      <dob>1996-8-16</dob>
      <deactive>0</deactive>
      <type>2</type>
      <status>1</status>
      <created>1474510510</created>
      <day>16</day>
      <month>8</month>
      <year>1996</year>
      <phone>0933858367</phone>
      <address>12 Võ Văn Kiệt p. Nguyễn Thái Bình q.1</address>
      <country>vn</country>
      <city>30</city>
      <skype/>
      <facebook/>
      <is_newletter>0</is_newletter>
      <is_received_email>0</is_received_email>
      <fb_load_newfeed>1</fb_load_newfeed>
      <fb_load_photo>1</fb_load_photo>
      <city_text_vi>Hồ Chí Minh</city_text_vi>
      <city_text_en>Ho Chi Minh City</city_text_en>
      <lat>10.768619</lat>
      <lng>106.7028058</lng>
    </db>
  </userinfo>
  <user_cv>
    <db>
      <ui>3293</ui>
      <title>Nhân viên phục vụ, Pha chế</title>
      <experience>7</experience>
      <category>14,15,17,20,35</category>
      <type>2,4,6</type>
      <level>2</level>
      <lang>vi,en</lang>
      <s1>0</s1>
      <salary>1</salary>
      <about>My name is Thiên Kim. I’m now a junior of International University, major in Hospitality and I’ve never done a part time job before. Actually. I want to do jobs that give me chances to learn something new and meet a lot people. I’m an extrovert and enjoy social and communication activities so I believe that would help much in the position for which I’m applying. I don’t think I’m any more or less special than other applicants. However I do have good qualities like sincerity, loyalty and reliability which I feel are important traits for a person to possess. Besides, I can easily make good relationships with colleagues and they can always count on me in both good times and bad. A person like me will strive to do a great job, serve the best service to customers, if not an excellent one then only get satisfaction from a job well done. If you require any further information from me then please get in touch. In any event, I look forward to hearing from you as the recruitment process progresses</about>
      <skill/>
      <keyword/>
    </db>
  </user_cv>
  <appliedjob>
    <total>6</total>
    <strjo>126,222,201,181,371,211</strjo>
  </appliedjob>
  <education>
    <n_691>
      <id>691</id>
      <school>HCMC International University</school>
      <degrees>Undergraduate </degrees>
      <fieldofstudy>Business Administration ( Major in Hospitality)</fieldofstudy>
      <from>2014</from>
      <to>2018</to>
    </n_691>
  </education>
</information>
