<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <userinfo>
    <db>
      <id>67</id>
      <email>ohviecvn@gmail.com</email>
      <username>chill-sky-bar</username>
      <name>Chill sky bar</name>
      <im>67_chill-bar-logo.jpg</im>
      <gender>0</gender>
      <category>14</category>
      <phone>0908059590</phone>
      <address>106 Hồ Xuân Hương</address>
      <city>30</city>
      <dob>0000-00-00</dob>
      <type>1</type>
      <status>1</status>
      <created>1459651228</created>
      <size>1</size>
      <website>www.chillbarsaigon.vn</website>
      <facebook>https://www.facebook.com/like.chill.saigon/?fref=ts</facebook>
      <is_newletter>0</is_newletter>
      <fb_load_newfeed>2</fb_load_newfeed>
      <fb_load_photo>2</fb_load_photo>
    </db>
  </userinfo>
  <totalJob>1</totalJob>
  <userbanner>67_chill-cover.jpg</userbanner>
  <more>
    <about>CHILL Skybar + Dining is a modern stylish and vibrant club, lounge bar and dining that offers both entertainment nightlife and social dining experiences destination. It is notably the first and the original “Skybar” concept in Vietnam. It is perched atop of the AB Tower in the bustling District 1 of Ho Chi Minh City and situated exclusively on the 26th floor of the city skyline.&#13;
The venue comprises 10,000 square feet with high floor ceiling and a dining mezzanine in a state of the art development office at the AB Tower in the heart of central Saigon, which would benefit not only surrounding vibrant nightlife but also commercial clientele from the prestigious shops and offices in the area.  CHILL is located adjacent to the New World Hotel.</about>
    <whyworkus>Chill Skybar Dining are among the industry leaders in nightlife entertainment and hospitality in Vietnam with training and job advancement opportunities as well as market-wide competitive working environment.&#13;
Should you be interested in career opportunities with us, please refer to our current job vacancies below. Potential candidates are cordially invited to fill in our job application form and email to recruitment@chillsaigon.com or send your Curriculum Vitae to:&#13;
Capella Entertainment Corporation</whyworkus>
  </more>
</information>
