<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<information>
  <userinfo>
    <db>
      <id>75</id>
      <email>thuetoday@gmail.com</email>
      <username>thue-limit1460479844</username>
      <name>Saigon Ranger</name>
      <im>75_saigon-ranger-logo.jpg</im>
      <gender>0</gender>
      <category>14,15,16</category>
      <phone>01267543789</phone>
      <address>5/7 Nguyễn Siêu, Bến Nghé, Hồ Chí Minh, Việt Nam</address>
      <city>30</city>
      <dob>0000-00-00</dob>
      <type>1</type>
      <status>1</status>
      <created>1460479844</created>
      <size>1</size>
      <website>https://www.facebook.com/saigonranger/</website>
      <facebook>https://www.facebook.com/saigonranger/</facebook>
      <is_newletter>0</is_newletter>
      <fb_load_newfeed>2</fb_load_newfeed>
      <fb_load_photo>2</fb_load_photo>
    </db>
  </userinfo>
  <userbanner>75_saigon-ranger-cover.jpg</userbanner>
  <more>
    <about>At this very moment, Saigon Ranger has become widely popular with international travelers and local citizens who are passionate in high quality live bands with endless entertaining nightlife in Ho Chi Minh city.&#13;
&#13;
We offer a variety of international dishes along with cocktails, coffee and soft drinks.More importantly, we strive to delight your time here with regular special cultural events like Art Exhibitions, Workshops, Venues and etc. We also privatize our space for events and parties.&#13;
&#13;
Come over and experience our events for yourself!</about>
    <whyworkus>Saigon Loves Jungle summons the spirits of jungle past, present and future to a new haunt: The SAIGON RANGER, where sinister subsonic vibrations and bone-shattering breakbeats animate the raving horde.&#13;
&#13;
Saigon Loves Jungle are hosting their third charity fundraiser for Green Youth Collective, coming this Halloween to the Saigon Ranger. SLJ DJs will be unleashing monster jungle and drum &amp; bass anthems from 10pm to 2am. Dress up scary to win prizes on the night.</whyworkus>
  </more>
</information>
